http://www.weberandrose.com/privacy-policy

Contact
Privacy PolicyWeber Rose, PSC considers the privacy of its web patrons to be extremely important.  If you have any questions about our policy please contact us. This statement (hereinafter “Privacy Policy”) applies to information collected online from users of www.weberrose.com and www.weberandrose.com (hereinafter the Web Site).  During your use of the Web Site, information is collected in three ways: 1) directly from you; 2) from server logs; and, 3) from cookies.  This information is used to personalize your experience.  We do not share this information with third parties, unless expressly indicated herein, or unless we believe, in good faith, that the law requires disclosure.  This privacy policy only applies to the information contained on the Web Site, and Weber Rose, PSC is not responsible, nor does this policy apply to information collected from any other source. This website is not intended for use by children.  If you are under the age of 18, you should use this website under the supervision of your partners or guardians, and you SHOULD NOT submit any personal information herein. If at any time you wish toknow or make corrections to to the data has been collected about you, you may contact Weber Rose, PSC at the number provided on this Web Site.  Additionally, you may request that information be corrected or deleted.   Information You ProvideYou may choose to voluntarily provide certain personal information to Weber Rose, PSC via the website.  Please do not submit any confidential or personal information (e.g. Social Security Number; date of birth; driver’s license number; or credit card, bank account or other financial information).  Any such information will be submitted by you at your own risk.  As set for in the Website Terms of use, NO ATTORNEY CLIENT RELATIONSHIP exists until a formal relationship is agreed upon and you are accepted as a client.   Web Server LogsWhen you visit the Web Site, Weber Rose, PSC may track certain information and store that information in web server logs, which record activity on the Web Site.  The Web Site uses google analytics.  Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit the site, rather than your name or identifying information.  We do not combine the information collected through the use of google analytics with personally identifiable information.  Although google plants permanent cookies on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit the site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but google.  Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Web Site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy.  You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits by disabling cookies on your browser. Examples of information collected by the web server logs may include:Your IP addressThe city, county and state from which you accessed the Web SiteThe kind of browser or computer you useThe name of your internet service providerThe number of links you click within the Web SiteThe date and time of your visitThe web page from which you arrived to our Web Site The pages you viewed on the Web SiteSearches and queries you conducted via our Web Site This information helps us improve your experience and helps us learn from your use of the Web Site. CookiesWe use “cookies” on this Web Site.  Cookies are bits of data that are sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive.  These cookies help us provide a customized and personal Web Site experience and applications my use cookies to store and help track information about you.  The use of cookies is relatively standard and allows you to do things like save your passwords and preferences.  Cookies do not store information that would allow Weber Rose, PSC to personally identify you, nor do they obtain any information from your computer. Most web browsers store cookies automatically; however you may choose to disable them.  By disabling cookies your use of the Web Site may be limited in some ways.  LinksThis Web Site may contain links to other web sites.  Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other web sites.  We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Web Site and to read the privacy statements of any other web site that collects personally identifiable information.UpdatesOur Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at the number provided on this Web Site.
Back to Top
Weber Rose, 471 W Main St #400, Louisville, KY 40202(502) 589-2200
Privacy Policy   |   DisclaimersAdvertisement MaterialPhotography: Whitney Neal  |   Design: RachFost
